securityfocus.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement for www.securityfocus.com

SecurityFocus has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **www.securityfocus.com**. 

State Management

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save identification information to authenticate you. In this way you are automatically signed-on each time you visit your site. 

Data Collection

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), and optionally, demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company only if they have explicitly requested so. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services if any are requested. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

External Links

This site contains links to other sites. www.securityfocus.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, mailing lists, message boards, and/or news newsgroups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us or our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. In order to unsubscribe from a SecurityFocus mailing list manually, use your email program to send a blank message to listname-unsubscribe@securityfocus.com, only replace the word listname with the mailing list's name. For example, to unsubscribe from bugtraq you would send a blank email to bugtraq-unsubscribe@securityfocus.com.   
Remember that once you have done this, you must still reply to the confirmation email that will be sent to you shortly afterwards. 

Contacting SecurityFocus

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [webmaster@securityfocus.com](mailto:webmaster@securityfocus.com).
